Why haven't you left yet?
I was organizing the materials
involved in the flight control review.
Wu Wei, you kid,
what's going on?
What work did I assign you?
Have you finished organizing all these files?
I finished organizing them.
Organizing?
And I even improved the search system.
The search system?
Okay.
This thing is actually quite useful.
I also made a review plan myself.
Please take a look.
I saw we had so many good materials,
Come.
so I just casually put this together.
Let me see
what you've written.
Nan,
how many cups of coffee is this for you today?
If you push yourself so hard,
I won't be able to keep up.
How can I not be anxious?
Think about it. If we can't even do the simulation well,
who's going to assign us tasks in the future?
Nan,
you're already doing great.
The data you've done
is already much more than ours.
Cai Bo'ao,
can you stop with the endless praise
and non-stop talking?
You don't see the work that needs to be done,
and you don't produce any results.
Have you finished your tasks for today?
Qu Ruonan,
I beg you,
stop spreading anxiety, okay?
I'm anxious too, really.
How can I not be anxious?
I'm telling you.
What a coincidence.
I just dropped by to visit.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I'll go in and take a look.
I'm telling you,
doing it well and doing it fast,
we have to hit at least one.
I haven't even finished speaking.
You guys,
this place of yours is really nice.
Um,
can I take a look at your plan?
Do you know what we're doing?
Isn't it just a review?
When you came to my place a couple of days ago
to get materials, I saw it all.
I also studied it a bit.
It's quite difficult.
You're also doing a review?
No.
I just noticed when I was organizing the files
that the Ark-8 mission had
a similar situation.
Actually, you can go to my place to take a look.
From review rehearsals to launch materials,
we have everything.
Will that be useful?
It will definitely be useful.
Take your review, for example,
it's the most basic plan
among the rehearsal plans.
And there were several upgrades after that.
Then how about we go take a look.
It wouldn't hurt anyway, right?
Trust me.
You guys will definitely gain something.
Right.
Let's give it a try.
Let's try.
Try it. Let's go.
Let's go.
Try what?
I know the way. I don't need you to lead me.
Who wants to lead the way for you?
I'm leading the way for Bao and Nan.
Slow down, guys.
No one told me
that joining flight control requires a physical test.
These rookies are really rash.
Don't worry, Mr. Qin.
I will reiterate
our discipline here to them later.
They can't work with this attitude.
Running is better than lying flat.
This fish, Wu Wei,
is finally in the right place.
Fish?
What fish?
Catfish.
Catfish?
Rendezvous and docking
comes from
the spacecraft system.
Ark 8
is our first space rendezvous and docking.
So,
only considering
the space laboratory system is not enough.
You also need to consider space platforms,
space transportation, and a series of other contents.
I have already
organized these materials.
I will send them to you later.
Space City Archives
Thank you, Wu Wei.
You helped a lot.
Wei.
All of this on here,
did you do it in this archive?
Yes.
Wu Wei,
from now on,
I can't call you brother anymore.
You are
my savior.
Sorry about before.
I always thought
that there were only files in that archive.
I didn't expect there to be a
sweeping monk.
Right.
You're welcome.
Nan, Bao.
I said,
this is a sutra pavilion.
Here,
although it is a small archive,
it stores the essence and efforts of our predecessors.
It has everything you need.
It's a pity
that some people are blind
and don't know what's good for them.
Who are you talking about?
Who?
Who knows?
Don't be happy too early.
There is a problem with your plan.
A problem?
What problem?
That's exactly what I meant.
You didn't write this step.
The whole plan is wrong.
Derived from my plan,
this is the result.
I can't be bothered to argue with you.
You're just being stubborn.
Alright.
We have the plan.
Let's get to work.
Okay.
Nan,
take a look.
Mr. Qin,
the newcomers' review report,
what do you think of it?
Who came up with this plan?
Is there any problem?
Was it your suggestion?
No.
Then you guys came up with it together.
Very good.
You're making fast progress.
It was Wu Wei.
Who?
Wu Wei from the archives.
Are you busy?
Qin,
what's the matter?
Let's finish that game of chess from last time.
Sure.
It's rare for you to be so proactive.
Come on.
But we have a deal,
if you lose, you have to promise me one thing.
You...
Just tell me what it is first.
It's not like I'm going to eat you.
I just want to...
That Wu Wei,
lend him to me.
For what?
What do you mean lend him to you?
What do you think this place is?
A fish pond?
Release fish when you want,
and cast the net when you want?
Let me tell you,
no. I won't.
Don't be so quick to say no.
Listen to my reasons.
What reasons?
Are you not confident
in your chess skills?
Okay.
You even learned how to use reverse psychology.
Fine.
Look,
the picture I took last time.
Right, bring the picture.
Watch closely.
You...
Don't show me that.
I memorized it all.
You memorized it, right?
Of course.
Okay, I'm ready here.
No, you...
The cannon wasn't here.
Don't touch it. Of course it was here.
Look.
It's just like in the picture.
See clearly, okay?
Let me see.
What are you looking at?
Give me the phone.
Let me see.
The photo is wrong.
You can't fool me with this photo.
Can photos fool anyone?
Pictures are the truth.
Otherwise I won't play. I won't play.
No, no. Okay, okay, okay.
Just be down-to-earth.
Just sit, sit here and play.
You have so many problems.
It's still wrong.
The photo obviously looks like this.
Still not.
Okay, okay, okay. Play.
It's wrong.
Make your move. Go on.
Move.
That's right.
Th-That's right.
Exactly. Move.
Check.
Your turn.
How... What is this?
Wu Wei!
Where is Wu Wei?
I just saw a shadow pass by.
I thought it was Wu Wei.
Come on, it's my turn, right?
Right.
Make your move.
Move.
Wait.
When did your horse get here?
It's always been here.
When did it get here?
No.
My cannon was blocking your horse.
You couldn't have jumped over.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you.
You remembered wrong. It's here.
What do you mean?
Of course you remembered it wrong.
Are you playing tricks on me?
When I turned around,
you moved it, right?
The horse was not here.
I was calling Wu Wei,
and saw a shadow flash by.
Look carefully. Look carefully.
Look where the horse was last time we paused.
What's going on?
Okay, okay, here.
Dead.
It's a deal.
Keep your word.
Wu Wei is mine.
You said he wasn't reliable anyway,
right?
You don't like him either.
Let me borrow him.
Wu Wei.
How is the file organization going?
The Haoyue mission part is almost done.
I think it won't be long
before the "landing" step proposed by the chief designer
in the three-step strategy of "orbiting, landing, and returning"
can also be completed quickly.
Looking at the review files,
I feel the speed we overcome difficulties
is getting faster and faster.
Do you know why?
Our equipment is getting more advanced,
and we prepare more and more contingency plans.
Not to mention rendezvous and docking,
even a different separation angle of two spacecrafts
will have several plans prepared.
The more preparation,
the fewer malfunctions.
For us aerospace workers,
our favorite word to hear is 'normal'.
I think flight control will
definitely improve in ground
and orbital technology.
And the simulation system.
Wu Wei.
Deliver this
to Flight Control 1020,
Mr. Qin's office.
Wu Wei.
Mr. Qin,
were you looking for me?
Yes.
Come here.
This...
Mr. Zhao asked me to bring this to you.
What is this?
How is it?
Did you learn anything at the archives?
It's pretty good.
To be honest,
when I first went to the archives,
I wanted to use it as a stepping stone.
But after I got there,
I realized it's a real treasure trove.
In the face of our predecessors' experience,
I truly feel insignificant.
I've read the plan
you helped the Muxing team with.
It's very interesting.
Really?
Thank you for the compliment.
Do you want to join them in the simulation flight?
Simulation flight?
Simulated flight control.
To see your plan put into practice.
Can I go too?
That depends on you.
But Mr. Zhao probably won't agree.
And my work at the archives...
Consider this an extra learning opportunity for you.
As long as it doesn't affect your main job,
I think it should be fine.
You can take some time to think about it.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
I'll be leaving then.
You're back.
Did you deliver the stuff?
What did that old man say?
He said
he wants me to join the simulated flight control mission.
But I'm still hesitating.
Wait, you're still hesitating?
What's there to hesitate about?
Mr. Zhao. Mr. Zhao.
Don't use the knife.
No,
did you forget what you studied?
Go do what you're supposed to do.
Let me tell you,
there are no cowards in the archives.
That old man is my nemesis.
If you lose to his people,
you're humiliating me.
Just wait and see how I deal with you when you get back.
That won't happen.
I definitely won't lose.
I mean,
you've been with me for so long.
How come you haven't learned any presence?
Can you show some spirit?
I will absolutely not embarrass you.
That's more like it.
Do the mission well.
I know that look.
You're eyeing my pen, aren't you?
Just do this job well for me.
Then I'll tell you
who gave me this pen.
Tell me who gave it to you.
What else do you want?
Shouldn't it
be passed down?
You wish.
Finish the task first.
Excuse me, everyone.
I was very inspired
by your previous review plan for the
rendezvous and docking of Dragon Boat 1.
So the center's leadership unanimously decided
to add simulated flight control
based on the review,
to see whether this plan is
feasible or not.
But we've never done that before.
You hadn't done the review plan either,
but you did it well.
But simulated flight control is
quite different from the plan after all.
I'm worried that
with only three of us,
we won't have enough hands.
That's why.
That's why I found you another person.
Wu Wei.
Wu Wei?
You all know him.
I know Wu Wei came up with a lot of good ideas
for the previous plan.
So I want him to give it a try too.
I really appreciate
the atmosphere of you young people working together,
discussing and communicating
when you encounter problems.
In aerospace work,
innovation is a constant thread.
We need both innovation and breaking old ways.
Who do we need for innovation?
Me.
It must rely on you newcomers.
Wu Wei.
From today on,
you'll join the newcomers of the Muxing team
to complete the simulated flight control work.
Are you confident?
Yes.
Absolutely. Of course.
Definitely.
Your temper.
Does this count as an official transfer?
Well...
If you show me your efforts
and if you can
complete this job well,
I will consider
officially transferring you to flight control.
But
your work at the archives,
you cannot slack off either.
Otherwise, I won't be able to explain
to Mr. Zhao.
Rest assured completely.
I definitely won't delay. Keep your voice down.
the work at the archives.
For the simulated flight control,
I'll give you a 100% perfect result.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Okay.
I will definitely seize this opportunity.
You're still going?
Hurry up and save time.
Let's do our best together.
Waiting for your good news.
Please take care of me, Chu.
Good for you.
Xiaoying,
striving for China's aerospace,
understood?
Letting the rookies participate in the simulation flight
is fine with me.
But as for this personnel arrangement,
I don't quite understand it.
What's wrong?
Letting a newly hired archivist
participate in the mission,
isn't it a bit hasty?
I knew you would have an opinion.
But if you have an issue, come at me.
It was my idea.
Jiajia,
he's your junior from the same department.
As his senior, you should guide him.
Most importantly,
with these rookies,
don't you think
we need a catfish like Wu Wei?
But a catfish must have real strength
and ability.
He has strength,
passion, and ideas,
and played a key role in the review mission.
But the simulation flight is an online task.
There can be no mistakes.
Just let him try.
If he doesn't have the strength,
he won't stay in the end anyway.
Right?
Okay, I got it.
I'll go assign them tasks.
Jia,
I won't let you down.
You four,
meeting.
The simulation flight
is the most important part of the review work.
It realistically simulates
the entire rendezvous and docking process,
verifying whether the task can be successfully completed
under the review plan.
It requires your cooperation.
The time is set for a week from now.
Wu Wei,
since you proposed the plan,
you are responsible for perfecting it.
Before work ends today.
Get to work.
Let's go too.
We're colleagues now, right?
Work hard,
and remember to hand in your homework before work ends.
Friends,
from now until work ends,
don't bother me anymore.
I'm going all out.
Come on, Brother Wei.
It's your first day at flight control.
Don't push too hard.
What's the saying?
A step too large will tear something.
Tear.
Brother Bao,
the first homework must be decent.
So now we...
I say, Cai Bao,
can't you learn something good?
Have you finished your part of the plan?
Well,
it's getting competitive already.
I'm almost done.
I'll wrap it up and send it to everyone soon.
I'm eating.
The war has just begun.
Ying,
you are more capable than all of us.
Can you give us a break?
What? You want to work overtime?
Caibao.
Better to rely on ourselves than on others.
Let's get it done.
Ourselves.
So your proposal
is not up to standard here.
Mr. Chu,
during the interview,
you didn't really approve of my abilities.
And you didn't agree with Mr. Qin
transferring me from the archives.
But I've been working really hard lately.
I just want to know
where exactly
I fell short.
Alright, let me ask you.
The revised part of your proposal
refers to the automatic docking plan
of Ark-8 and Dragon Palace-1, right?
Yes.
Didn't you notice any problems with it?
Let me give you an example.
Suppose you're flying the latest fighter jet,
but the engine is from ten years ago.
How far could it fly?
After the technological innovation,
the previous algorithms and parameters are no longer applicable.
It's good that you are willing
to refer to and learn from them.
But your biggest problem
is that your foundation isn't solid enough.
I hope in the future,
I won't have to explain these things to you.
This is my standard for you.
Have I made myself clear enough?
Alright, take it back and revise it.
I'll show it to you after I revise it.
And
remember,
in real space missions,
there is no chance for revision.
It's a shame.
A shame.
What's wrong, Wei?
What a shame.
Stumbling so hard on the first task.
Why didn't I think of
what Jia said?
Start all over again.
For our team's debut,
we have to show we are grounded
and make a big impact.
Innovate and forge a new path.
Wei,
you're using big words now.
Since you got out of the archives,
your perspective
has really broadened.
But I think Wu Wei is right.
The opportunity Mr. Qin gave us
is to let us prove our worth.
I worked hard since I was young
and got into the center
on my own merit.
If we don't have the determination
to innovate and find a new path,
how can we secure our place here?
It's the weekend tomorrow,
Wu Wei,
I'll work overtime with you.
Is everyone free tomorrow?
I'm free.
We're all geniuses here, right?
Qi,
are you going home this weekend?
I'm fine with anything.
Then it's settled.
Tomorrow morning at 8:00,
in our dorm.
We can eat, drink, and discuss.
Okay.
Today went pretty smoothly.
Very well.
My back hurts again.
Let me tell you,
you should get that old problem checked out.
Don't ignore it.
I've seen doctors several times, but it hasn't helped.
You didn't drive today, right?
I'll give you a ride.
You're so nice to me.
Why are the lights still on?
Wu Wei.
He fell asleep.
Although his foundation is weak,
he has a good attitude.
What's the use of a good attitude?
Without ability, it still won't work.
No, I'm serious.
I just took a look at this version of the plan.
The changes are bold.
I think it's quite interesting.
Seems like he's stuck on the parameters.
Comrade Chu Jiajia,
I've realized something.
You're the same every year when mentoring newbies.
A sharp tongue but a soft heart.
Let me tell you, it's a thankless job.
These kids are all scared of you.
Like a demon king, right?
You know it.
Wu Wei.
Jia, Yan.
If you're done, hurry back.
Do it tomorrow.
Good work.
No worries.
We'll get going.
Okay.
Good work.
It's nothing.
I heard a hot pot place opened nearby.
It has great reviews.
How about we go wild for a bit?
We could.
I noticed Qin is very anxious this year
to get results from the newbies.
You don't need to rush.
It puts a lot of pressure on me.
Jiajia.
Ziming, why are you back?
You didn't even tell me.
Mr. Zhang.
Long time no see.
Ms. Li.
I've been waiting a while.
Look how romantic he is.
Waiting for you here
to give you a surprise.
When I asked yesterday,
you said the task would take half a month.
I don't know how,
but once the task went smoothly,
I came right back.
Smoothly.
Hey, watch it.
I haven't left yet.
You must be hungry.
Come eat hot pot with us.
Up to you.
I haven't even digested my lunch yet.
It's been a long time.
You two should spend some time alone.
It's fine. Let's go together.
Mr. Zhang,
take Jiajia out for a nice, big meal.
Why don't we go together?
No, I'm not going.
See you on Monday. Bye.
Bye, Mr. Zhang.
Bye, Jiajia.
You drive.
Let's go.
Cheers.
Have a seat.
Look,
if my transfer this time
goes smoothly,
I want to have
a clearer plan for our future.
There's something
I want to discuss with you.
What is it?
I heard that
the center is about to
evaluate professional titles soon.
You need to take this seriously.
You must get it.
It will also help with your job transfer.
Job transfer?
Transfer where?
To administration.
With a higher title,
the benefits will be better after the transfer.
And an administrative job has regular hours.
My work needs your support.
You also need to think more about our future.
So what do you think?
Look,
after my promotion,
the benefits and everything will definitely improve,
but I'll also get busier.
We can't both be busy.
Let's not talk about this for now.
Let's eat first.
Jiajia,
I know you have your career to pursue.
But
for the sake of our family,
one of us has to make a sacrifice.
You can't just avoid it
every time we talk about this topic.
I'm serious this time.
I hope you can take my opinion seriously.
So you're saying
that between the two of us,
I have to be the one to sacrifice?
If I don't sacrifice,
I'm being irresponsible to our family?
I think
you still have to make a choice.
Since we started dating,
I've always been the one accommodating you.
You do whatever you want
and go wherever you want.
When have you ever considered me?
I hear you.
You're asking me to choose between you and my career.
Let me tell you,
I will absolutely not leave flight control.
Eat by yourself.
Space people, space spirit,
striving to be the best in flight control.
Striving to be the best in flight control.
Get up.
Get up. Get up.
Hurry up and get up.
Are you done?
Get up for the meeting.
It's already 7:30.
They'll be here any minute.
Isn't it at 8:00?
They're coming for a meeting.
Shouldn't you clean up a bit?
Hurry up and clean up.
Go, go, go.
Aerospace people, aerospace spirit.
Striving to be the best in flight control.
You haven't washed up either, have you?
They're almost here.
Brought breakfast for everyone.
Morning.
This place is so clean.
This living room is
spotless.
Who cleaned it?
Welcome.
Let's look at the bedroom.
This room is really clean.
Wei.
This is your room, right?
It's so messy.
Why didn't you clean up?
After all, Nan is a girl.
Nan.
Don't blame Wu Wei.
He probably doesn't see you as a girl.
Caibao.
Look at my fist.
Is it big?
But to be honest,
the hygiene of our dorm
in the Aerospace City
is definitely a model standard.
As the saying goes, if you can't clean a room,
how can you sweep the world?
Qi looks like someone who does great things.
I cleaned all of that.
Thank you.
I cleaned all of this.
What are you doing, Wei?
Just woke up?
Hurry up and brush your teeth.
We're waiting for you to eat breakfast.
Go.
The coffee Qi makes is so good.
Isn't that annoying?
Just drink your coffee, flatterer.
Let's start with
confirming the final plan.
Agreed.
Especially the fast rendezvous and docking plan.
We need to confirm
which one to finally use.
I think our current plan
is still too conservative.
There is a lot of room for optimization.
We can consider using radial pulses directly
from below the target orbit to move upwards.
The advantage of this plan is the short approach time,
and the low propellant thrust,
which eliminates intermediate steps.
So you mean
we should readjust the plan?
That would mean a lot of parameters and algorithms
to resolve.
We'll make it in time if we work overtime.
Besides, Mr. Qin and Jia also said
that for the first simulation mission,
they want to see our own ideas.
Trust me, you two.
Our Muxing Team
will amaze everyone.
Make a splash.
My plan
will definitely help us complete the mission,
and show Mr. Qin and Jia the true capabilities of me, Wu Wei,
and our Muxing Team.
What do you think?
As for the plan,
I think it's indeed quite challenging,
but...
What do you think, Qi?
Stop asking what he thinks.
Tell us what you think first.
Me?
Your parameters are inconsistent.
This plan won't work.
My parameters are inconsistent?
No, these aren't the parameters I wrote.
Isn't this your plan?
Jia, Yan,
if you're done, hurry back.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Someone definitely changed my parameters.
The references don't match up.
Let's just stick to the previous plan.
You haven't even figured out the parameters.
No, wait.
Even if my parameters are wrong,
it doesn't mean my plan is wrong.
I am confident.
This plan will definitely work,
and it better reflects our ideas.
Really.
Sticking to the previous plan is the safest bet.
We just need to perfect the subsequent steps.
Why?
When there's obviously a better choice,
why not take it?
Besides, this plan is very feasible.
There are many historical precedents we can refer to.
Because it's unnecessary.
Can you stop trying to be a slacker
and goofing off all day?
Can you put in some effort, Ying Ziqi?
Alright, you two.
Just talk about the ideas.
Yeah.
Nan.
I'm just focusing on the matter at hand.
I really don't believe
that with your abilities, Ying,
you'd think my plan is unfeasible.
Besides, I went to the archives
and checked a lot of relevant information.
With our abilities, it's absolutely not a problem.
I didn't say your plan is unfeasible.
Then why not do it?
The purpose of the mission
is to use the safest plan
to ensure the successful completion of the simulated flight control.
Not to show off.
Don't impose your personal goals
onto the team's mission.
Just having ideas isn't enough.
What do you mean by that?
Choosing a better plan
and trying hard to prove my abilities and ideas,
is that wrong?
You don't need to prove yourself.
You don't need to prove anything,
not because you're so strong,
but because you simply don't care.
To be honest,
I think
Wei's plan is quite challenging.
But after all, this is
our Muxing Team's debut.
It's better to play it safe.
Wei,
I know you've been in the archives,
that 'scripture library',
and you'll surely achieve greatness.
But we'll have opportunities in the future.
We don't have to rush this one, right?
Qu Ruonan,
say something.
I don't know what to say.
But Wu Wei,
I appreciate your attitude and determination.
As for the proposal,
I lean more towards Ying Ziqi's.
Although compared to yours,
it's a bit too conservative.
But his proposal
is safer and more reliable,
and backed by more data.
Yes.
I admit with my current abilities,
it's hard to convince you all.
But I really think we should try.
It's just a simulation.
Why can't we test it?
What are you afraid of?
We aren't afraid,
and we don't distrust you.
We just want to
complete the task,
that's all.
But you weren't like this before.
Where's that drive you had as a kid?
Ying Ziqi.
I might not be as capable as you,
but at least I'm willing to try.
You were specially recruited.
You took a spot
that so many dream of.
What are you here for?
You clock out on time
and play games in the dorm.
What have you achieved?
We're a team, aren't we?
Right?
Now I seriously doubt your attitude.
You don't cherish this at all.
That's none of your business.
Of course it is.
Enough.
Stop arguing.
Just because it's called a dorm,
do you still think you're high schoolers?
I don't care about your past grudges.
That has nothing to do
with today's proposal choice.
Since everyone has ideas,
let's go with whoever has
the highest overall score.
Okay?
The specific proposal
will be decided the day after tomorrow.
Nan.
Aerospace Flight Control.
Sorry to bother you, Mr. Chu.
I want to ask you
about my proposal's parameters.
The parameters are inconsistent.
Did you change them?
What do you mean, Wu Wei?
Mr. Chu helped you so much.
Are you misunderstanding something?
If you changed them,
why didn't you tell me?
Yes, I changed them.
Because you cited the wrong parameters.
The reason I didn't tell you
was hoping you'd check the rest yourself.
Is there a problem with that?
Don't you check
your own plans?
My parameters just weren't accurate enough.
You could have told me if you thought they were wrong.
And how did you know
that was my final plan?
Just not accurate enough?
Wu Wei, you work in aerospace.
In our industry,
there is no room for error,
otherwise it leads to catastrophic disasters.
And you have the nerve to tell me it just wasn't accurate enough?
Forget it. It's nothing.
Go back to work.